A long time ago,
it is said, a monster came here.
There it is.
Sarii.
Circle back.
...the trial.
...my trial.
Fetch.
...orange flowers.
...orange flowers?
Crazy.
...orange flowers.
-What's going on?
Fetch.
Ouch. Ouch.
Hurry up!
I'm cold.
Stand still.
No.
Go!
Your trial.
Here.
Here!
...your trial...
Taabe comes! Taabe comes!
Come.
Come with me.
Now.
Buffalo spirit, fly well.
Thank you, Creator, for your life.
-a monster.
That's bad.
Look Here.
A woman?
What is she doing here?
I will carry her.
She's gonna slow us down
No.
By the way she was running,
I think she saw it.
That's your new blonde, huh?
Get that fucking dog off me!
I don't have a good feeling about this.
Are you Angry?
Now you will pay.
We'll see what she knows
-Speak, dirty Raphael.
-What are you doing here, huh?
-It's a trap ?
-What is happening?
I'm going to kill her.
We can always use her.
I will make her sing.
Bring out the savage.
Get him out of the damn box!
One way or another,
you're going to help us.
Make it bleed.
We shouldn't have brought the horses.
Shut them up or the beast won't come.
...your trial?
Where is this whore beast?
I'm hungry and I need to pee.
What is happening?
Oh, no, no, no.
What is happening? Rambert!
Shoot, Rambert!
Shit.
He's there!
That is some crazy shit.
Now!
We have it!
Bastard!
Shoot!
We will hit the others!
Spread. Get away!
Let's hurry a little.
I need help.
We can't do anything for them.
We just have to keep moving forward.
And the dog?
I love the dog.
It tastes better than beaver.
Go find Taabe.
Cheater!
Nope! Oh no! No stop!
Whore!
Idiot savage.
You don't even know
the mistake you just made.
I will put a bullet in your skull.
You're gonna die, bitch!
Demon!
No!
Fetch!
Naru is coming here!
Arüka, here! Arüka, Naru comes.
Naru comes.
What does she have?